So guys, finally, all four brothers are ready.
I am made yellow.  And look in my hand, I have
taken this also.  To cut this,
whoever needs to be cut will be cut with this.  And
here is Sahil who is made green.  and
Kunalli Red.
Six.
very nice.  One two.
Six again Papa ji, six again.   No. No.
One
again six.
Brother, Piyush also wants three and Sahil
also wants three.
Hey guys, good morning.  Welcome to my new
vlog.  So guys, in today's video we are going to
play such a big Ludo.  Guys,
you must know that we
also played a very big game of Saasadi.  So guys today we are going to play
Ludo this big.   Guys, it's going to be a
lot of fun playing this.
And where is Sahil Lada?
He has
not yet woken up.  I am sleeping, friend.
This is the biggest task.
What?
That both of them have to be picked up.  Without those two, the
game wouldn't be the same.  Yes guys, four of us will
play, we four brothers.  And we will choose each color one by one.
But for that one must have four brothers.   Should be.
Where are the two brothers?
Two of them must be sleeping.
Let's pick them up first then.  Guys, we have made the
setup ready.  Look here,
Ludo has also been played.  I have also brought big dice here.
And carpet has been laid here.
So we will throw away the carpet.   Throw it.
This is how it has to be thrown.  Like four has just arrived.
Four?  Like this, six can come, two can come
, one can come, anything can come,
guys.   Let us go.
So guys, look from above how cool Ludo looks.
Yes friend, look how big Ludo is in the living room
brother.  It will be fun to play.  Let's
pick them both up then.   Let's
first pick up Sahil and see.
Hi Lada.   Get up.
We are playing Ludo.  A very
big one.
When will you open it, it
seems it is not coming at all,
what should I do,
you play, I
play in his place,
I am already playing,
respect, get up, we have to
play a game, Ludo, a very big one,
Kunal, come on, you keep hanging till Piu opens it,
keep hanging till Pizza opens it, okay.   Let's see whether I am able to
complete the task or not.  Do
n't come down until he opens it.   Let's see.
Hey, come quickly.   Do
n't come down, you will lose.
What happened?  Will I get anything?   Are
?   Will you
get anything for winning?
Yes, yes.
What?
Your favorite thing.
[nasal sound]
In the feet.   Stay
stuck, stay stuck.
Hey, your legs have become crooked.   Stay
stuck, stay stuck.  Otherwise, you will lose.   Get
stuck, you will lose.  Press the feet.
Press your feet and hands immediately.
I have suppressed it completely, yet it is still coming.
Brother Piyush is not opening it.
[ __ ] brother
lost.  We both can play but it is
not a game for two people.
Can you play?
Only two people can play?
Easley.
Now see.  You people say go out with the family.
How do you go for a trip, brother?  Two people remain
sleeping peacefully.  And Kunali does
n't like to go out like that.  So I will not go alone.
Go with.  Guy is
n't opening either door.  neither.  We
tried very hard.  And guys, it is not that the
time is very early.  I'll show you the time.  It's about to be
12:00.  Look, it's 11:54.
So you are not getting up yet, friend.
What should we do with them?
Guys, now we will have to wait for Sahil and
Piyush.  Whenever he wakes up after 1, 2, 3 hours, only then will
we continue the game.  So
let me show you today
what is our struggle in planning something.  I have to
pick them up.
They have to face the main struggle.  They have to be brought down.  Kunal,
when you grow up, will you also remain asleep
or will you wake up?   Get up.
Sure, let's see.   So
I just get up.   Let's see.  Let us go.   I still get up.
See,
earlier Piyush also used to get up.  Guys, it's been
an hour since we've been waiting.
Neither of them has come yet brother.
Because Piyush was saying that I am coming.
But Avantika has come here
ready.  Come on, there are three of us now.
Kunali one who can come along?
Elder father came in Rupa's vest.
What to play?  Ludo.
Will you play?
Yes.
Kunali it's 2:00.  It's been 2 hours.   I am
sleeping for 2 hours brother.
Hey, go upstairs, I am calling him, son.
Knocking on the door, both of them will not get any money.
We have done everything.  So let's have lunch for now
brother.  The food is ready.  Kunalli has
made chole.  Will you eat chickpeas?
So guys, I am ready to
wear red.  Who is on my team?  Finally
Sahil has come after calling for 2 hours.  Well, at least
Sahil has come.  Now what time will Piyush come,
guys?  The food is ready.  Let me do one thing, I will
pour water completely into Piyush's mouth.
No, it does
n't mean that he has grown up.  Ok.   I
pour a whole bucket of water into it.
Do we do it?  Who knows what he is doing
here?
So guys, finally I am also ready.
Today I have become yellow because yellow is
our colour.
[laughs] Let's
dance too.
This is it
friend, I should also wear my lehenga.  You should have told me also.
So guys Avantika and I are choosing yellow colour.
So we are both on the same team.  And
the rest of Kunalika is red in colour, so it remains red.
Look, the whole place is red.
And Piyush is coming so Piyush will choose blue.
We are forming teams of two.
One will throw the dice and one will play.
For example, suppose I am here, then a person will
throw the dice.  So it's going to be fun.  You will enjoy it
brother.  Let's see who will win today's game.
Yes, you can do it like this also.  Hey, what do you say
?   Hey ya.
What is he doing?  Are you mad
?   This is
my T-shirt, take it off.
What?   I
know it.
So we also have weapons to cut guys.
Look, we will use this when we have to cut.
Look at this.  Kunali has this.
I have this.
What else will have to be cut?
Hey, if we have to bite each other, we will
bite with this.   I will
hit you straight away.
No, no, I will cut it with this.  So guys, finally all
four brothers are ready.  I am made yellow.
And look, I have this in my hand too.
To cut this, whoever needs to be cut, they will
cut it with this.  And here is Sahil who is green
and Kunal is red and finally Piyush has also
come who is blue.  Look at this.  So let's
see today who will win this Ludo game.  And there are
four people here to roll our dice.  The
big one is Blue which is on Piyush's side.
Avantika is yellow which is on my side.
And aunty is on Sahil's side.
Green and Badi Mummy are on Kunali's side.
So everyone will roll the dice from our side.
We ourselves will not throw it away.  We will be here in the game, right?  So that's why
we have hired our family members to throw the dice.  So let's
go and if we get out then tell me he will
come.
And yes, if I get out then
Avantika will come in my place and let's see
who reaches here first.  Whoever reaches here first will
win.  The first thing to
get here is Guys.  So let's see, let's start the game.  Come on, come.
So let's start.  Ok?
GUYS [applauds] Finally I'm open.
I will go here now.
So no game.
No, no, play.  Let's go to Bade Aaba's turn.
Big father.   Oh no no, I have to take you around
completely brother.   If
this happens, you can cheat on anything.
Four did not open.
Aunt's turn.
Kunali?  It's elder mother's turn, brother.
Kunali's turn.  Throw the big mummy.
Hey, throw it from here.  Wait, you take it.
Throw it from here.
Yes.  Four yes not open let's go
one or six I do
n't have to see two
two
brother don't do any cheating don't give it after seeing yes let's go
straight
two
so I am going one two I am going in front of everyone till now
so let's go
three
I will stay here I will stay here I
these are not opening yet the
beans are coming.  The beans
opened.
Well, the other
shore has opened up.
Come on brother,
three,
one, two, three,
Sahil has arrived.
Three three
one two three
three [laughs]
brother brother
Piyush is not opening at all brother.
Yes, which did not open
three three
both are coming quiet our.
Come on
four four
one two three four three three
one two three this star is
safe you
what is this star?
I am safe, safe, safe here.  Ok let's go.
Why this?
Hey friend, poor Piyush will be sitting there,
guys.  Look, I am
not able to eat Vadaapa brother.   He
will sit there for four drains, he is already sitting there.
Aunty
strategies fake vadapa.
Let's throw auntie throw auntie.
Six o
one two three four five six.  Oh brother.
Leave it, cut it.  You will enjoy it.  You are talking too much.
Okay cutting.
Oh brother.
Three one two three
one two
brother can you cut me Sahil
five
one two three four five are you
safe again
guys five
and brother how are you at the same place guys we
both will
not be cut at the same place here
this entry button has
opened one more turn one more turn one more turn
guys Kunali has also opened.   There will
be another turn.
Five
one two three four five.
Hey,
finally my stone has also been opened.
Finally.
Now you know
anyone can get cut, brother.
Yes.
Now let's see some danger,
who will be cut first brother.  Let us go.
Sahil's turn.
Four.
One, two, three, four.
So now let's go, I will come from behind.  Let us go.
Four.
One, two, three, four
guys, now Piyush can bite me.  I am four.
If Piyush gets four, I will be out
brother.   Had
fun.
[laughter]
One, two, three, four.
And we took out our sword and
brother, what a bad luck we have.
What guys, I have to go back.
Now Avantika will come.
Guys, now Avantika has come here in my place.
Now I will throw Avantika's dice.  Let us go.
Five one
two three four five come on brother
one come on
son [sound of clearing throat] come on
one
where are you throwing it it's
my turn guys so I have to take
out Avantiya I need one or six annas only then will I be able to come
out let's see what will
come
oh three
guys I think we can lose the match
friend.
Large numbers are needed to divide the system.
Big number
three
came in very big.  One, two, three
is fine.   Five five.
one two three four five.
Two
guys hopeful that Avantika will get out this time.
Oh friend, it's five.
One by one
[laughs]
Let's turn.
Say five five brother.
one two three four five.
Brother, the message
brother, now it will not open when it comes here, I
will cut it from here.
Come on Aunt
Five.
Five 1 2 3 4 5
Hey Sahil, it's about to end brother.
Cut to Silda
yes it is about to end.  It's going to end there, friend.
Oh my guys, our luck is very bad today.   Give two.
Come on brother.   It was
my turn.
Three one two
three.
Big one for me.   Stand up.
Three
one two three
what are you doing brother?  I am in danger.
Oh, I have come brother.
Well, it's my second turn.   Now
a friend can
bite you like a Kunali.
Can cut.   Oh, yes.   Bye bye.
One two three four five six.
Let's have one more.   I am in
danger, I have gone away
son.
Five
very good very good one two three four
five safe friend let's go
good
four
okay one two three four
brother is right behind you
roll
anything can happen do
n't cut
three bring it just do it somehow four four one two three four
my turn
brother now something big should come otherwise Pawan will
cut Avantika
Kunalli
six is
saved
one two three four five six once
brother
four one
two three four come on
now a little one one
whose one is mine yes one come on
what is this
earlier six five came
two one two
one the
game is over like different come on
brother bring six six
we can win again
yes bring six quickly
two has come two
let's increase it big this time increase it
four one two three four not bad
six one two three four five six one
and one and come on
three
one two three you roll from 10 here
okay big let's
six
one two three three four five six come once come once.
Three three one two
three.
Hey
brother, he is going to win.
Hey, I'm going to win.  Brother, I am going to win.
Oh brother,
one, two, three
brothers, cut the silo quickly, friend.
Bring six quickly then.
They need five of mine, they will be safe and then
no one can cut them.
Guys, now we will have to cut the silo.
Six to five Six to five.
Hey friend, are you coming?  Not just one,
friend, one came.  Hey friend, let's
not get cut ourselves now Kunali
six five
five three four
five
Mummy please bring five the
fifth son son, whatever comes, that's enough
three three two the
head doesn't come, neither do I have to turn it around, it does
n't come
with two whose
friend should get six
one two three
four
guys Sahil is going to win why do I
feel like this Sahil is going to win
six very good one two three four five six it came again again
six papa ji again six no no one
again six let's go one two three four five six
again six no the
turn will get cut
thrice six turns get cut I
need five five five six six five
best brother one two three four five
and I need only three to win three and
I will win
three one two
three
hey quickly bring a big number make a
big number and no one can cut me come on
complete
one two three four five six
brother I also need three Piyush also needs three
brother Piyush also needs three and Sahil
also needs three see where Piyush is standing
one two three one two three
now let's see who among these two
will win this game?
Oh brother.
Who will get three first and only three should be given.
If you get six, it will not be accepted.   You
won't get six.  The turn will be cut.   The
turn will be cut.
And even if you get four, it will not be accepted.   The
Their turn will be cut.
We can go either two, three or one.
Now it is my turn.  Now I have three.  I
will win this.
Come on brother, we have already lost.
Three let's go by three.
Six.   Nothing will happen.  Nothing will happen.
Let's go to my turn six.
Two
okay guys look one two three let's go winner is
cheating
winner guys hey guys so
today's winner is
great guys it was fun
Piyush won guys he came last of all let's go
I am the one to win it let's
play for second let's play for second
now let's see who comes second
Piyush has come first let's see who comes second come
whose turn is it start
come forward.   No no,
we are playing right now.  Piu won, right?
[sound of clearing throat]
three
one two three
just [sound of clearing throat] one was
so close you know if three four had come then
we would have been cut off.   Let's
go one.  Now I need two.
Aunt and
friend will probably be cut off.   I am from
two.  I am the same.   I am the same.   It is
not ours.   If it's
not, it's
good, isn't it?
won.
We won.
Okay
guys, I think the second Sahil can come now.   I am
bringing only one.   I have got
a key, friend.
One got stuck.  Now I am trapped.  I only need one
now.  Now I am trapped.
Stop it, Allah, do it,
four,
one, three,
5000, son, take some air from my hand,
how will you not cut it, you
six,
six, my
one, guys,
I might come last,
hey friend, bring any number in the big one.   Let us go.
Any number
five.
one two three four five.  I need number three guys.
Yes, somewhere.
Brother Kunal wants three and Sahil
wants one.  So let's see
who comes second between Kunal and Sahil.  Come on brother.
Four did not come.   Let us go.
Hey friend, three have come.
One, two, three.   Do
n't bring more than three, just
bring three
[screaming voice] bring one each, guys, like this also,
now both of you want one each,
look both of you are standing at the same place,
five
three, hey friend, what has happened, like this you will
definitely not win,
six
friend, you are bringing two, friend.
How about two friends?
Come on brother, second one has come.
Let
me come third.
Oh, here comes another one.   Let's
go four by four.
Two
two
hey friend why am I bringing only two I am
feeding two, swing it straight ok like
this
five
one two three four five
oh brother
swing it straight the big one straight two
why are you bringing only two
hey two
son how will you throw it straight?   Come on like this,
I'm throwing, I'm throwing.
Then refuse it anyway.
Oh okay, I'm throwing it away.   Nothing will happen.
Two
straight.
[screaming]
Well, we could have come first.  Ours got cut.   Guys, I had
fun playing the game.  Piyush
won and we came last.
I am the winner.   The
thrower sometimes wins.   I had a
lot of fun.   It has to be
thrown long.
Big she she came.  The trick has arrived.  The one
that was throwing the big one to the big dad was coming.
Elder father was throwing it from where
he was.  They were doing the same to him.   Guys, I
enjoyed today's game.
Tell us how you liked it by commenting.  For now, I'll
end this video.  See you
in the next video.  Thank you so much for
watching.   Bye.
[Music]
Guys, look, our video has been shot now.
This is how I shoot daily.  I will
call him first.  Then they do
not come.  Then they come like this in two-three hours.
Today I showed you the entire process.  To
call you, to pick you up.
Look, he is having breakfast right now.  Having
breakfast at 4:00 p.m.  Chole
rice.  It was right.
[Music]